<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>
	<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
		<mods>
			<li>VGP Vegetable Garden</li>
		</mods>

		<match Class="PatchOperationSequence">
			<operations>



				<!-- VPE Apples to Granny Smith Apples -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_AppleTree"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>granny smith apple tree</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_AppleTree"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A tree bearing hard apples, with a light green skin and crisp, juicy flesh. The flavour is tart and acidic. It remains firm when baked, making it a very popular cooking apple used in pies, where it can be sweetened.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_AppleTree"]/graphicData/texPath</xpath>
					<value>
						<texPath>Patches/Plants/VCE_GrannySmithAppleTree</texPath>	
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawApple"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>granny smith apples</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawApple"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>Hard apples, with a light green skin and crisp, juicy flesh. The flavour is tart and acidic. It remains firm when baked, making it a very popular cooking apple used in pies, where it can be sweetened.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawApple"]/graphicData/texPath</xpath>
					<value>
						<texPath>Patches/Raw/VCE_GrannySmithApples</texPath>	
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Banana to Gros Michel -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_BananaTree"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>gros michel banana tree</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_BananaTree"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A tall tropical tree adorned with a cluster of yellow, elongated berries. These trees have been genetically modified to resist the fungal infections that nearly caused their extinction in old Terra. The Gros Michel variety has a distinct taste, different from that of Cavendish variety bananas. Bananas are easy to harvest, since a whole "hand" can be cut at the same time.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
			
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawBanana"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>gros michel bananas</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawBanana"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>Yellow, elongated berries. These bananas have been genetically modified to resist the fungal infections that nearly caused their extinction in old Terra. The Gros Michel variety has a distinct taste, different from that of Cavendish variety bananas.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Cherry to Sakura -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_CherryTree"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>sakura tree</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_CherryTree"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>Also known as the cherry blossom, Sakura trees produce small fruits known as sakuranbo, small cherries that do not have much flesh beyond the seed within. Due to their bitter taste, sakuranbo are not traditionally eaten raw, but these trees have been genetically modified to produce sweeter tasting fruits. This particular genus is quite beautiful, speckled with pink blossoms throughout, blooming fully each winter.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
			
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawCherry"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>sakuranbo</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawCherry"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>Small cherries that do not have much flesh beyond the seed within. Due to their bitter taste, sakuranbo are not traditionally eaten raw, but these fruits have been genetically modified to have a sweeter taste.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Orange to Mandarine -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_OrangeTree"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>mandarin tree</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_OrangeTree"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A small citrus tree with fruit resembling miniature oranges, usually eaten plain or in fruit salads. Mandarins are smaller and oblate, rather than spherical, like the common oranges (which are a mandarin hybrid). The taste is considered less sour, as well as sweeter and stronger. Mandarin trees are well equipped for growing in humid environments and in wet soil.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
			
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawOrange"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>mandarins</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawOrange"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A small citrus tree with fruit resembling miniature oranges, usually eaten plain or in fruit salads. Mandarins are smaller and oblate, rather than spherical, like the common oranges (which are a mandarin hybrid). The taste is considered less sour, as well as sweeter and stronger.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Eggplants to Black Beaty Aubergine -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Eggplant"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>black beauty aubergine plant</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Eggplant"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A bulbous, tender, tasty purplish-black fruit of the nightshade family. Aubergines or eggplants are great in a variety of dishes, and the Black Beauty variety is delicious grilled, baked and stir-fried. Flourishes in warm weather.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawEggplant"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>black beauty aubergines</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawEggplant"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A bulbous, tender, tasty purplish-black fruit of the nightshade family. Aubergines or eggplants are great in a variety of dishes, and the Black Beauty variety is delicious grilled, baked and stir-fried.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Peach to Apricot -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_PeachTree"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>apricot tree</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_PeachTree"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The apricot is a fruit that resembles the peach but much smaller, pale yellow or orange with some red shades. It is mainly consumed fresh, although it is also used to make some by-products like stewed fruit, jams, juices and dried apricots. Apricots have a high concentration of vitamin C. This variety of apricot tree is quite hardy, and they can be planted in stony soil.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
			
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawPeach"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>apricots</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawPeach"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A fruit that resembles the peach but much smaller, pale yellow or orange with some red shades. It is mainly consumed fresh, although it is also used to make some by-products like stewed fruit, jams, juices and dried apricots. Apricots have a high concentration of vitamin C.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Pumpkins to Mammoth Gold Pumpkins -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Pumpkin"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>mammoth gold pumpkin plant</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Pumpkin"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>One of the biggest varieties of pumpkin, the mammoth gold can grow to between 25 and 50 Kg of weight. Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest. However, their durability means added weight and mass - Too cumbersome for hydroponics basins.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawPumpkin"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>mammoth gold pumpkins</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawPumpkin"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>One of the biggest varieties of pumpkin, the mammoth gold can grow to between 25 and 50 Kg of weight. Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Tomatoes to Red Beefsteak Tomatoes -->

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Tomato"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>red beefsteak tomato plant</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Tomato"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A variety of tomatoes with a firm, meaty, rich, vibrant red colour. Its flavour is mild, juicy and balanced compared to other varieties. Tomatoes are easily removed from the vine without having to uproot the plant.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>

				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawTomatoes"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>red beefsteak tomatoes</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_RawTomatoes"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>A variety of tomatoes with a firm, meaty, rich, vibrant red colour. Its flavour is mild, juicy and balanced compared to other varieties.</description>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<!-- VPE Grass to Forage Grass -->
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Grass"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>forage grass</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_TallGrass"]/label</xpath>
					<value>
						<label>forage tall grass</label>		
					</value>
				</li>
				
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_Grass"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
								<description>Cultivated forage grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground.</description>

					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace"> 
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName="VCE_TallGrass"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
							<description>Cultivated forage tall grass. Grows anywhere there is a little light and minimally fertile ground. Slows down anyone moving over it.</description>

					</value>
				</li>
				

			</operations>
		</match>
	</Operation>


</Patch>

